What I love about Grand Strategy Games is
that you set up your own goal...
...like unite Germany
...conquer the world
...or just draw something childish
...but I've never seen anyone try to
...but I've never seen anyone try to CAPTURE SANTA.
Yes, now you're probably saying:
"Silly Kilian, Santa isn't real."
"It's impossible to deliver
presents to billions of people in one night."
Oh, he's very real, but he's not the happy fat guy...
...he's a lot more like Jordan Belforch...
...except Santa snorts children's happiness.
And delivering all those presents is not impossible...
...just highly improbable.
You are making the logical fallacy that a
God-like creature sees time the same way we do.
Gunna play the current day mod for extra challenge.
Actually, let's change it to 2014...
...was a better year.
In these types of videos, I usually play as the good guys.
But today, we are naughty,
so I'm going to play as the Villains.
"But Kilian, Santa lives on the North Pole."
I have one thousand hours in this game.
Yes I know, I'm still a beginner,
but I'm pretty sure there's no North Pole.
Don't worry, he's not there.
Early December,
Santa is in his vacation house in Finland.
All we have to do is take over this Finnish region...
...and also the Netherlands.
Europe can have only one silly language.
Finland *would* destroy us in a military conflict...
...but because it's 2014,
Finland isn't one hundred years old yet...
...so they still have to share regions with older siblings.
*sharp gasp*
It's a Christmas Miracle™.
If we caught Santa, we should get a
"Kris Kringle Captured" event...
...but we do not so, we failed.
Video over.
(not really) (i guess you knew that)
Too bad, I was looking forward to, um...
Another event!
Christmas Joy™ is slowly consuming the world.
I have to stop it before
Christmas Eve when he reaches...
...MAXIMUM CHRISTMAS MAGIC.
Yes, that's also a real thing.
That's what they use over at SpaceX.
*Low Groan, in disappointment*
I can't do it.
I need more time.
Time.
Wait. Of course!
I'll just download the Time Travel Mod!
It uses the most
scientifically correct time travel theory ever.
That's how passionate EU4 fans are for authenticity.
Also, if you think I'm going
to establish a bunch of time travel rules...
...that I'll follow...
...you are VERY delusional.
Everything just works, don't question it.
Now I can change events that created Santa's Empire.
December 8th, and I literally have all the time in the world.
What made Santa so powerful was Mass Media...
DAMN YOU CHARLIE BROWN
...so we need to stop Hollywood from happening...
...and the only way to do that is to arrest...
...(Christopher) Columbus, so he never makes his business trip.
He's dead!
Let's Return!
America will now be very different....
I meant a different kind of different.
I see.
Because Columbus never discovered America...
...and no-one else ever did.
We don't know what the New World would look like.
It might not even be there.
Schrödinger's Yanks.
(I remember seeing this at TED, interesting stuff)
Because of this move, I lost Greenland.
My first line of defense.
Making me an open target.
It's December 13th.
I still have some time...
...maybe a better idea would be to take back
Human Technology several hundred years.
By erasing the three events that fast-forwarded the world:
The Printing Press
The Printing Press,
The Advent of Electricity
The Advent of Electricity,
Halo:Combat Evolved.
I can destroy them all.
Now, if I go back to 2014, we...
Ah.
That's a surprise.
This would be even harder to defend.
I can't deal with a Reindeer Space Armada™.
December 18th.
This Christmas scourge is going to kill me.
Unless, I kill Christmas.
I've been thinking about this all wrong.
We don't need to stop Christmas...
...if it was never invented.
According to "The Actual True History of Earth"...
(It's a great book, had it for school.)
...written by me.
Christmas was invented by Augustus (Caesar).
His quote:
I'll send a "jenmag" assassin to
stop that from happening.
Augustus Caesar is dead!
I can't remember who his heir was...
Uh ohhhhhh
Oh no.
I have to get back to my time!
FAST!
December 23.
Tommorow is Christmas Eve.
I have only ONE option left.
I have to go back to the beginning of civilization
and kill Santa as a baby.
There.
Back to the Stone Age.
You can see that because every country is a rock pun.
Now we just have to find where Santa was born.
What's going-?!
He's...
He's a MONSTER.
An unstoppable authority of power.
I can't get back to 2014!
Nooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo...
Santa: "Ho ho ho."
Santa: "Hello Kilian."
Are you here to kill me?
Santa: "No."
Santa: "I am here to deliver your presents."
It's...
An uncooked broccoli.
That's everything I've ever wanted!
This has put me in a better mood.
I feel Joy!
Christmas Joy™!
*sudden shock*
I've been assimilated!
Damn you, Santa.
DAMN YOU TO A SNOWLESS CHRISTMAS!!!
Subtitles done by san7890 :)
(sorry if you don't like the quips i put in there)